(line ringing)
STUART:
This is Debbie!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
And this is Stuart!
BOTH:
Just kidding!
STUART:
Leave a message!
(beeps)
(whispers):
This is the part where you talk.
(Dan:)All right, let's say
a physician was prescribing
(Dan:)one of our competitor's drugs.
(Dan:)How would you convince them
to switch to ours?
(Sheldon:)Um...
(Penny:)any chance his car needs
(Penny:)to be washed by a girl
in a bikini?
(quietly):
No...
(Penny:)Okay, I'm really sorry
for wasting your time.
(Dan:)Don't worry about it.
Thanks for stopping by.
(Penny:)Okay, thanks.
(Penny:)Um, I'm sor...
Listen, could you do me a favor
(Penny:)and not tell Bernadette
how badly I blew this interview?
(Penny:)She'll get upset.
(Penny:)And honestly I'm a...
a little terrified of her.